Guide to the Don Brockett Papers, 1930-1998 CTC.2002.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Orchestrations, V.
  - Unknown Composers, 3.
    - Peaches and Bananas Opening (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Picture Production (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Pilgrim Indian (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Opera (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Playmate (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Pledge of Allegiance (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Portia and Ben (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Pothole Polka (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Public TV (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Racing with the Clock (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Robert E. Lee (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Rolling Rolling (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Saintly Swinger (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Salvation (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Santa Claus March (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Sheboygan (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Shepard and Angel (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Shuffle off to Buffalo (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Sing Along (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Sisters (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Six Months Out of Every Year (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Some of These Days (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Stewardess (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - String of Pearls (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Strutaway (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Susie (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Swanee (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Sweet Adeline (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Sweet Georgia Brown (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Tapflash (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Telephone Number (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - TV Themes Game (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Thanks (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Thank You (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - This Time of Year (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Tin Whistle (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Toast of the Town (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - To Life (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Tradition Vamp (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Trees (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - We Beseech You (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - We're in the Money (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - We's be in da Moaney? (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Will You Still Love Me Tomorrow (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Winchester Cathedral (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - WQED (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Yesterday He Asked Me (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - You're a Santa's Helper (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - You Can't Miss It (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Misc./Unidentified Songs (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Other Orchestrations, 4.
    Boxes 29 and 30 are medley orchestrations and are in an alphabetical arrangement by title. Box 30 also consists of a number of items that are all assorted orchestrations and were grouped together by Brockett. For the most part, the orchestrations are not published materials, and sometimes are handwritten. Some of the song titles have very extensive orchestrations that include music for a full orchestra. Box 31 contains original Brockett orchestrations that are not available for access to patrons due to their condition, although copies have been made and are available for use with the other copies of music for that song title.
    - Medley Book #1 A-I (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
    - Medley Book #2 J-Z (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
    - Broadway Medley (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Chevalier Medley (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Chuck's Christmas Medley (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Commercial Medley II (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Commercial Medley No. 3 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Diet Medley (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - The Don Brockett Memorial Medley (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Fiddler Medley (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Gospel Medley (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - New York Medley (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Night Medley (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Patriotic Medley (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Patti Burns Medley (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Performance Medley (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Romance Medley (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Star Wars Medley (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Wonderful Night Medley (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Audition Music (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - George Cohen Salute (w/medleys) (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - '93 Music (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Benefit (music/letters/program) (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - "Special Music" (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Brockett written orchestrations A - Z (Restricted due to condition) (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
- Photographs, VI.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by folder subject title. The folder subject titles are the same folder titles that were present on the folders when the collection was received; they were probably titled by Brockett.
  - Brockett and Barbara photos (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Brockett and Barbara's 25th anniversary (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Burlesque pictures (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Celebration '76 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Celebrity photos (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Celebrities (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Don with celebs (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Don Brockett with friends (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Do Wah Diddy (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Early photos (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Forbidden Pittsburgh (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Gimbel's (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Industrials (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Marriott shows (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Melodrama (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Mr. Rogers (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - X-Mas pictures (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Misc. labeled photos (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified (Box 34, Folder 1-5)
- Oversized and Miscellaneous Materials, 1970-1998; VII.
  The final series in the collection contains items, information, and promotional materials with entertainers that Brockett managed and worked with, such as Jack and Sally Jenkins, The Vogues, and Father Tom Smith. The Index to Music in Theatre resource is a partial alphabetical list of Brockett productions along with cast lists and the song titles that were performed in the show. This series also contains some miscellaneous and/or oversized photos, art, and plaques.
  - Index to Music in Theatre (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Jack and Sally Jenkins (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Father Tom Smith (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Before and After calendar with original artwork, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Sweet Feet plaque – autographed by cast (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Framed caricature of Brockett as Sophie Masloff (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Gold record plaque for Turn Around, Look at Me by the Vogues (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Oversized and Miscellaneous Art and Extraman comic strip (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Oversized Photos (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Unused "Public Relations Consultant" Brockett letterhead (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Framed photo of Brockett balancing bottle on his head (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - New Forbidden Pittsburgh 1998 laminated poster (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Framed Big Bad Burlesque collage (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Big Plastic Don Brockett head (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tonight poster (Box 36, Folder 5)